Contact

8888164364 (Mobile) pranitdhoke@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pranitdhoke (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microservices
Spring Boot
Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Languages

Marathi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Professional Working)

Certifications

Oracle Certified Professional, Java SE 6 Programmer
Certified ScrumMaster® (CSM®)
Java Multithreading

Pranit Dhoke

Technical Lead @ e-Zest solutions.

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in JavaServer Pages (JSP), Amazon EC2, SQL, Oracle Database, and Maven. Strong engineering professional with a PG Diploma in Advance Computing focused in Computer Software Engineering from Center for Development in Advance Computing (Headquarters).

Experience

e-Zest Solutions Technical Lead January 2019 - Present Pune Area, India

John Deere India Pvt. Ltd. (JDTCI) Senior IT Data Analyst I August 2018 - January 2019 (6 months) Pune Area, India

NICE Systems
Software Engineer
August 2015 - July 2018 (3 years)
Pune Area, India

Persistent Systems
Senior Software Engineer
February 2015 - August 2015 (7 months)

Synechron Software Associate March 2012 - January 2015 (2 years 11 months) Hinjewadi Phase II

Education

Center for Development in Advance Computing (Headquarters)
PG Diploma in Advance Computing, Computer Software
Engineering · (2011 - 2012)

MET's Institute of Engineering
Bachelors Of Engineering, Information Technology · (2006 - 2010)

KTHM Junior College HSC, Science · (2005 - 2006)

A.P.Patel High School SSC · (2003 - 2004)